A Guide to the R. E. Gish Papers
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #595
R. E. Gish Papers 1871-1892
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
595
75 items and 8 v.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 1939 August 29
Biographical Note
R. E. Gish was a Lynchburg, Virginia tobacco merchant.
Container List
- Papers
  - Accounts of European sales, 1887-1892
- Bound Volumes
  - "Factory Book" - Company store accounts of factory workers, 1871 May-Dec
  - Record of cash accounts, 1871-1878
  - Ledger - contains orders and cash accounting, 1883-1891
  - Order book, 1885-1890
  - Shipments received book, 1886-1887
  - Accounts of British firms with whom Gish does business, 1887-1889
- Oversize Volumes
  - Accounting Journal, 1885-1892
  - Checkbook for British transactions in pounds sterling, 1889-1892